CONTACT INFORMATION



+(57) 301 472 7920



sfg222@gmail.com



https://bit.ly/3vINUSz



Medellín, Colombia

EDUCATION

2005 - 2011

ELECTRONICAL ENGINEER

Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana

1003 - 2007

ACADEMIC BACHELOR

Colegio de la Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana

2014

ENGLISH C1

Shafston International College - Brisbane, Australia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- · Javascript
- Typescript
- · Angular 4+
- · Angular Js
- Actionscript
- · Visual Studio Code
- · HTML 5
- · CSS 3
- · Bootstrap
- · Angular Material
- · GIT
- · SCRUM

LANGUAGE

SPANISH

Native

Speaking, reading and writing

ENGLISH

Advanced - C1

Speaking, reading and writing

HOBBIES

- Photography
- · Video Games
- · Outdoor Activities
- \cdot Sports
- · Scuba Diving
- · Travel

SANTIAGO FLÓREZ GIRALDO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Front-End developer with experience in agile projects in the fantasy sports industry, publishing houses, insurance, consultancy, and taxes industries. Capable of adapting to new challenges and technologies, being a technical leader within the team, and promoting high performance and good practices. In addition, I have had the opportunity of working in interdisciplinary teams with direct interaction with the client, UX designers, and members of the Development team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Gorilla Logic

2020 - Current

Development of web applications using Angular 9, Angular Material, HTML and CSS. Implementing Angular best practices.

Unit test design using Karma and Jest.

User stories refinement together with the business analyst and the QA team.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Source Meridian

2020 - 2020

Development of web applications using AngularJs. Refactoring and implementing AngularJs best practices. Implementing responsive web design with Bootstrap 3.4.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Globant

2017 - 2020

Development of web applications using Typescript, Angular 2+ and Angular Material.

Designing web layouts using HTML 5, CSS 3 and Bootstrap.

Development of web applications using JQuery and Knockout JS.

Unit test design using Karma and Jasmine.

Deploying apps to DEV and QA environments.

User stories refinement together with the business analyst and the QA team.

Communication and close work with a development team and customers.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Betiply S.A.S.

2015 - 2016

Working together with the design team in order to develop a user-friendly interface for the siteand the mobile application.

Development of mobile applications for IOS and Android, using Ionic Framework.

Set up and configuration of TestFlight for mobile app testing (IOS).

Development of web applications, using AngularJs.

Setting up Nginx and SSL Certificates.

Development of back-end software and APIs using Express and Node JS for mobile and web app.

Deploying web app into DEV and QA environments.

Amazon DynamoDB queries Amazon Buckets configuration.

Web socket configuration for real time interface, using Socket.IO.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

INTEG.RO

2015 - 2015

Migrating platform for interactive boards from Actionscript to HTML5, Polymer and Canvas.

Formatting HTML content used for an on-line courses platform.

Attending meetings with clients in order to discuss required changes for the applications. Identifying and assessing client's needs.

Providing technical customer support as necessary

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Yuxi Pacific Latam

2011 - 2013

Development of ingestion and delivery workflows using Java.

Web app customizations using HTML and JQuery.

Web service customizations for efficient transit of content using Java.

Development and personalization of storage and content manipulation software in Marklogic for the IEEE.

Creation of XSLT files in order to transform between multiple formats on the fly.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Monitoreo Inteligente LTDA.

2011 - 2011

Development of desktop app using Actionscript to configure, administer and monitor GPS devices PostgreSQL database management.

Development of web services using PHP.

GPS devices programming and configuration.